NAISE PAUL

Mob: + 353899646667, naise paul@yahoo.co.in, naise paul@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/naisepaul

PROFILE:

I am a hard working, motivated and enthusiastic B.Sc.(Mathematics), Data Analytics Graduate having in depth knowledge and experience in technical and software aspects. I am having 19 years of work experience with 8 years of management experience. I have the ability to work independently and as a team. I am always ready to learn new things.

OBJECTIVE:

I intend to build a career with leading corporate in hi-tech environment with committed and dedicated people, which will help me to explore myself fully and realize my potential. I am accustomed to work as a key player in challenging and creative environment.

Educational Qualification:

Year of Passing	Board of Examination	School/ Institution
1999 - 2002	BSc. Mathematics	University of Calicut
2001 – 2002	PGDCA (Post Graduate Diploma in Computer Application)	
2016 -2017	Level 8 Higher Diploma in Science in Data Analytics	Dublin Business School
2023- 2024	Diploma in Full Stack Software Development .(E-commerce Applications)	Code Institute

Experience Details:

Clerical Officer - Garda Síochána October 2023 - Till date

Customer Delivery Assistant – Tesco May 2018 – October 2023

- Work efficiently to tight deadlines to ensure customer satisfaction.
- Deliver shopping to customers on time according to business needs.
- Keep regular communication with both customers and colleagues to update on progress and manage expectations effectively
- Check van for road worthiness.
- Make good Customer relationship and customer care.
- Planning and scheduling task in organized manner.
- Proactively work with minimal supervision on unexpected events.

Delivery driver - Camile 2018 March to 2018 May

- Deliver food to customers on time according to business needs
- Maintain good Customer relationship
- Communicate with team members to provide better service.

Data Analyst Intern – Popertee (NDRC) 2016 November–2017 June

- Reported to the CEO directly and converted the company requirements into data requirements.
- Extracted the data from the retail property websites and analyzed the characteristics of those properties for building the POC.
- Researched the API's to collect the Social Media data and initiated talks to get on with the Partnership agreements with LinkedIn and Twitter.
- Proposed the Data warehouse design and built a Physical SQL Server DW using Microsoft Azure.

Assistant Shop Manager - Apache Pizza 2012 July to 2016 November

- Coordinating staff
- Setting time tables and work schedules
- Ordering stocks
- Till operations
- Dealing with customer service issues

Senior Relationship Manager - Balance Equity Broking Pvt. Ltd (2011 March to 2011 May)

Senior Relationship Manager -India Info Line Ltd 2008 February to 2011 February

Dealer and Operation Officer - Religare Securities Ltd 2007 July to 2008 February

Operations Officer - Anagram Securities Ltd (Now Edelweiss Capital) 2005 August to 2007 June

Back office Executive - SSKI Investor Services Pvt. Ltd 2004 March to 2005 July

- Client acquisition Meeting clients, giving new product details and converting
- Franchisee acquisition For business development meeting people those who have franchisee to convert or new clients those who interested in new franchisee.
- Cross selling (Mutual fund, insurance) Sell mutual funds, insurance to existing clients or new clients
- Revenue Generating Generating brokerage from clients by advising market movements and from mutual funds
- Coordinating staff
- Risk management Helping the company that the clients position is not in bad debt
- Advising clients about stock market trends and risk Call the customers and tell them about their risky stock positions and recommending new stocks
- Petty cash Managing Managing the petty cash that we get from Head Office every month
- Accepting customer cheques and stock certificates Accepting the client cheques that they give for buying new stocks, converting old paper stock certificate to dematerialization
- Client account opening Fill the new account opening forms and sending to HO

Computer Instructor - Case Computers (Rajiv Gandhi Education Foundation) 2002 June to 2003 June

Assisting students in computer lab.

Certificate Courses/Workshops attended:

• MTA: Database Fundamentals – certified 2017

Technical Skills:

- **Python** Fundamental programming, Beautiful soup, Selenium, web scraping, panda, matplotlib
- **Database**: Studied about various databases and developed an SQL database for the hospital management system
- Jupyter Notebook- https://naisepaul.github.io/
- **R** Using the Boston data set, apply linear regression modeling to predict the per capita crime rate using other variables in the data set.

- German Credit data used to build a decision tree model for addressing a prospect filtering problem that identifies credit worthiness
 - **Tableau** Use the World Bank geo-coded Project data and apply Tableau to explore projects undertaken to-date to eradicate or significantly reduce poverty across the world by 2030.

Build a World Bank Project Progress Dashboard

- **Rapid Miner** Use the Boston Housing dataset
 - Identify which of several attributes are required to predict the median price of a house.
 - Build a multiple linear regression model to predict the median price of a house using the most important attributes.

Use the Garman Credit dataset to build a decision tree model for addressing a prospect filtering problem that identifies credit worthiness.

- **MS Access** Developed database system based on the normalised schema as a part of the assessment
- SQL Database System (Using MS SQL Server Management Studio)

 Microsoft SQL Server, tables and extract, transform and load North wind data set from the operational database into the data warehouse (data mart) using SQL queries.
- **MS Office** Excel, Word, Power Point

Achievements

- Excellent service Award (August 2018 Tesco)
- Best performer award in 2010 (south India- India Info Line Ltd)
- Managing customer relationships, identifying new business opportunities, developing marketing ideas, financial control and developing the team.

MY STRENGTH

- Willing to work on challenging assignments.
- Good analytical and interpersonal skills.
- Good problem solving skills
- Ability to take initiative for new things and flexible to learn.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Date of Birth 25-05-1982

Sex Male Nationality Irish

Address 9 Dunville Grove, Athulmney, Navan, Co. Meath

Reference: available on request

Declaration: I, Naise paul here by declare that the above information's are true to the best of my knowledge.